Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - "Front Page", stage reports, flyers, correspondence, reviews (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - "Galileo", design sketches (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - "Galileo", production notes (Box 159, Folder 28)
  - "Gemini", program and notes (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - "The General's Tea Party", correspondence (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - "Geniuses", reviews and programs (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - "George Brown and Friends", reviews (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - "Gertrude Stein", performance report and reviews (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - "Getting Out", correspondence (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - "Ghetto", programs and reviews (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - "Ghost Sonata", review (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - "Ghost on Fire", program (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - "Gideon", playbill (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - "Gilles de Rais", playbill (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - "The Gin Game", review and playbill (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - "The Glass Menagerie", program and reviews (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - "Glass Menagerie", background and reivew (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - "The Glass Menagerie", reviews (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - "Glengarry Glen Ross", playbill and correspondence (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - "Glengarry Glen Ross", Lit. Mat. (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - "God Bless you, Mr. Rosewater", reviews and notes (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - "God's Country", correspondence (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - "Godspell", review (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - "The Glorious Monster in the Bell of the Horn", review (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - "God Bless", correspondence (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - "Going Hollywood", correspondence (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - "Going Home", reviews and audio cassette (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - "Gold Dust", playbill (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - "The Golden Age", playbill (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - "Good", playbill and reviews (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - "The Good Person of Setzuan", reviews (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - article: Shakespear, Yes or No (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Ben Shaktman (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - correspondence:Barbara Shapira (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Pat Sheehy (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Mel Shaprio (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Steve Sheppard (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - resume and info: Ed Sherin (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Ed Sherin (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Pam Sherin (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Robert Shields (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Syliva Short (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Simon Siegl (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - information on signs for Arena Stage (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: John Silber (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Gintare Sileika (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Caren Silkwood (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Paul Sills (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Alan Simpson (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Issac Bashevies Singer (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Catherine Slade (Box 162, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Wayne Slappy (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Archie Smith (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Smith College (Box 162, Folder 23)
  - memo's: smoking policy (Box 162, Folder 24)
  - correspondence and info: SSD and C (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Andrew Sofer (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: South Coast Rep. (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: The Source Theatre Co. (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - resume: Hugh Southern (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - correspondence and info: SMU (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Anna Sokolow (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: The Soroptimist Society (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - notes and diagrams on stage problem (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: George Spalding (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - notes on speech: Stage Direction as a Profession (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Bob Crawford (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - stage four (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Gully Stanford (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - article: Stanislavsky (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Barrie Stavis (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Dorothy / Marie Stehle (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Howard Stein (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Roger Stevens (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Plays (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - article: Marcellus Stewart (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Bill Stewart (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: William Stone (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - info on Stone Henge and personal photos of Zelda at Stonehenge (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - correspoondence: Tom Stoppard (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - info: The Theatre Institute of Storm King (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Tony Straiges (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Steven Stosny (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Living Stage, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Living Stage, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - interview: Theatre Crafts, March 1984 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - grant information for Arena Stage tour of Eastern Europe, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - remarks: board of trustees, April 1984 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - remarks: Arena Stage campaign (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - remarks: tribute to Alan Schneider, May 1984 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - remarks: annual report, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - newsclippings: grant award announcement 1984 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - press information: NEA grant 1984 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - statement: NEA grant, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - ensamble grant package information, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - statement: Arena at 35 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - DOuble Image Theatre Honoree, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Speech: Helen Hayes Award, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - transcript: professional standards conference (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - remarks: Acting Company Award (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - article: Arena Stage at 35, notes, transcript and background (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - atricle: Arena Stage at 35, drafts (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - report: Arena Stage future plan. reserarch and background, 1984 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - essay: institution as art work (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - essay: institution as art work (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - The Illustrated Guide to America's Non-Profit Professional Theatres, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Theatre Profiles 7 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - newsclippings: Arena Stage at 35, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Award, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth Award, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Women and Theatre Awards Party, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - remarks: board of trustees, Feb. 1986 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - remarks: foreign visitors, March 1986 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - remarks: reception for Lyubimov, March 1986 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - remarks: NYU luncheon for Yuri Lyubimov (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - essay: the essential actor in American Theatre (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - essay: The Essential Actor in the Guthrie Theatre (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - remarks: Thomas Fichandler (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Helen Hayes Award, 1986 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - remarks: Board Dinner in Honor of Thomas Fichandler, May 1986 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - interview: NYU december 1985 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - remarks: May 1984 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - remarks: June 1986 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - essay: Arena at 35 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - remarks: The Alley (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - remarks: campaign recognition dinner, Sept. 1986 (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - essay: on risk and money, 1986 (Box 168, Folder 17)
  - artisitic statement, 1986 (Box 168, Folder 18)
  - NEA grant (Box 168, Folder 19)
  - articles: critics on criticism (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - notes (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - remarks: finance committee, Feb. 1987 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - remarks: board meeting, March 1987 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Zeisler Award, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Arena Stage thanks to long term workers (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - remarks: 1st rehersal for "The Crucible" (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - remarks: opening of "The Crucible" (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - remarks: Johns Hopkins (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - "Three Penny Opera", playbill and articles (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - "Through the Leaves", playbills (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - "Ti-Jean and his Brothers", program (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - "Time and the Conways", playbill (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - "Time of your Life", review (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - "The Time of your Life", reviews and sch. (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Tintypes: A Rag Time Review, 1978-1979 (wrapfile) (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Tintypes - A Rag Time Review, background info (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - "Tiny Alice", playbill and correspondence (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - "To Be Young, Gifted and Black", correspondence (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - "To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday", playbill (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - "Tom", playbill and correspondence (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - "Tomfoolery", audio tape, press release, playbill and correspondence (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - "Tongues", program (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - "Tooth of Crime", reviews (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - "Top Girls", program (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - "Topaze", correspondence and playbill (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - "Torch Song Triology", playbill (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - "The Tot Family", reviews, stage reports, etc. (Box 170, Folder 19)
  - "The Tot Family", script (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - "Total Eclips", correspondence (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - "A Touch of the Past", review (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - "Trackers", playbill (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - "Translations", reviews (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - "Travesties", playbill and reviews (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - "Trelawny of the Wells", playbill (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - "Trail of the Catonsville Nine", correspondence and program (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - "Trial of Mary Dugan", correspondence (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - "Tricks", correspondence, reviews and misc. materials (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - "Trilogy", program (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - "Trinidad Sisters", correspondence (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - "Trip to Bountiful", correspondence (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - "Trojan Women", playbill (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - "True West", reviews (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - "Twelfth Night", correspondence and reviews (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - "Twenthieth Century Tar", correspondence (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - "Twigs", playbill (Box 171, Folder 18)
  - "Two Blind Mice", review (Box 171, Folder 19)
  - "Two Gentlemen of Verona", program and reivew (Box 171, Folder 20)
  - "The Two Gentlemen of Verona", script (Box 171, Folder 21)
  - "UBU", playbill (Box 171, Folder 22)
  - "Uncle Vanya", playbill and review (Box 171, Folder 23)
  - "Uncommon Women", playbill (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - "Under Milkwood", correspondence and review (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - "Under the Gas Light", correspondence (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - "Under the Sycamore Tree", correspondence (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - "Undiscovered Country", program, correspondence and review (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - "Unlikely Horses", correspondence (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - NYU course materials (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - "12th Night", materials and program (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - speech: Dickinson College, Nov. 1976 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - notes (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - interview: background info, March 1977 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - notes on the new building (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - speech: 25th anniversary (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - panel discussion: Mark Taber Forum, April 1977 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Bob Prosky on 20 years at Arena Stage (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - speech: Boston University, March 1974 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - remarks: December 13, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - remarks: 25th anniversary (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - remarks: Arena at 25, January 1975 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - remarks: Arena at 25 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Ralph Collins Memorial Lecutre: Jan. 1975 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Ralph Collins Memorial Lecutre: Jan. 1975 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - the art of the director (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Womens Award, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings and program, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - statement of producing director, Jan. 1976 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - misc. speeches (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - essay: future of the performing arts (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - notes on Park School (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Commonwealth, April 24, 1978 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - back to basics (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - 1978 TCG conference report (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - essay: The Long Revolution (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - remarks: Staff and Company, May 25, 1979 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - speech: NEA. Aug. 11, 1978 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Curtin Winsor Lunch, Dec. 1978 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Thomas C. Fichandler, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence 1976 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - remarks: Isaac Bashevis event, Oct. 1979 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - remarks: The Director and Actor, NYU, Nov. 1979 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - speech: 30th anniv. kickoff party! March, 1980 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - 30th anniversary program (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - 30th anniversary toast, Oct. 1980 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - pre-benefit dinner speech, Oct. 1981 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - workshop: Boston University, July 1980 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - associate event, Oct. 1980 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - interview: Womens Roles, Aug. 1980 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - speech: Rotary Club, Jan. 1981 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Speech: John's Hopkins, 1981 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - humanities Symposium speech (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - TCG, January 1982 (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - annual report, 1981 (Box 177, Folder 14)
  - interview, 1982 (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - WETA women of achivement series (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Robert Alexander (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1978 (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1978 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1977 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1978 (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1978 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Thomas Fichandler: correspondence 1978 (Box 178, Folder 17)
  - Zelda Fichandler: misc. correspondence, 1970's (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - misc. notes and comments on plays by Zelda (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Zelda's notes on misc. plays (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Zelda's notes on misc. plays (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Zelda's notes on misc. plays (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - misc. letters from Zelda: 1976 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - misc. letters from Zelda: 1976 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - misc. letters from Zelda: 1976 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - misc. correspondence; 1973 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - misc. correspondence; 1978 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - misc. correspondence; 1979 (Box 180, Folder 17)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 180, Folder 18)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 180, Folder 19)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence; 1980 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - misc. correspondence; 1981 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - misc. correspondence; 1981 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - misc. correspondence; 1981 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - misc. correspondence; 1981 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - misc. correspondence; 1981 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Invitations to 30th Anniversary gala and planning notes (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - 30th anniversary planning notes (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - RSVP's to the 30th anniversary gala (Box 182, Folder 3)
    includes regrets from President Carter and Vice President Mondale
  - 30th anniversary material (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - 30th anniversary correspondence (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - 30th anniversary planning notes and memos (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - 6 30th anniversary programs (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry (Box 183, Folder 1)
    correspondence and information pertaining to Soviet Jewry and Arena Stage's tour of the USSR in 1973
  - information on the 1972 USSR tour (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - USSR tour sch., plans and information (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - USSR tour information including Russian entry documents (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - planning info for USSR tour, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - USSR Tour info (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - USSR tour information (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - USSR tour information (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Hong Kong arts festival; 1979 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    planning materials
  - long distance phone charges (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - long distance phone charges (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - long distance log sheets (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Hong Kong festival; 1980 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    offical banner, information and programs
  - Hong Kong arts festival: 1980 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    brochures and programs
  - Hong Kong arts festival; 1980 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    correspondence, articles and misc. materials
  - Hong Kong arts festival; 1976,1978 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    brochures
  - Hong Kong arts festival; 1980 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    programs (9)
  - USSR tour; 1973 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    misc. materials
  - Thomas Fichandler retierment event (Box 186, Folder 1)
    invitations and planning materials
  - Thomas Fichandler retirement event (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - 30th anniversary planning materials (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - 30th anniversary correspondence (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - 30th anniversary planning materials (Box 186, Folder 5)
    news clippings, "a look back at the 70's"
  - 30th anniversary planning material and 1980 annual report (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - 30th anniversary promotional materials (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - misc. materials (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Fichandler retirement dinner (Box 187, Folder 2)
    RSVP cards and planning materials
  - Thomas Fichandler retierment event (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Fichandler event (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage stationary (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - 30th anniversary promotional materials (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - 30th anniversary promotional materials (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - 30th anniversary stationary and bumber stickers (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - 30th anniversary planning materials (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - 30th anniversary promotional materials (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - 30th anniversary promotions (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - 30th anniversary promotions (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - National Medal of the Arts; 1990's (Box 189, Folder 1)
    nomination forms, invitations, correspondence
  - Washington Post Magazine, 8/5/90 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - misc. articles on Arena Stage (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - NEA grant materials 1989 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - NEA materials 1989 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - NEA challenge grant material, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - NEA cultural diversity program information, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Arena Stage fellows program information, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation, cultural diversity proposal, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - remarks: Ford Foundation Meeting, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Wallace Fund meeting, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Fund Services meeting, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Hitachi proposal, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Mellon Foundation; cultural diversity proposal (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - Mellon Foundation - grant proposal (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - Wallce Fund proposal, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - "Haiti", correspondence (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - budgets, 1987-1990 (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - "Merrily We Roll Along", negotiations (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - misc. files (Box 189, Folder 20)
  - future royalties (Box 189, Folder 21)
  - correspondence from LORT counsel (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - LORT - theatre classification (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - LORT correspondence (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: SSDC (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - LORT information (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - League of Washington Theatres (Box 190, Folder 6)
    correspondence and information
  - Theatre Quarterly newsletters; 1973 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Hong Kong arts festival (Box 190, Folder 8)
    budget
  - "Its the Truth if you Think it is", budget and financial information (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - "Summer and Smoke", financial information (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - "The Skin of your Teeth", financial information (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - "Avner the Eccentric", financial information (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - "Common Ground", financial information (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - "Antigone in New York", financial information (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - meeting minutes; department heads meeting on cultural diversity, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Playquest series (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - "Coming of the Hurricane", financial information (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - "The Plough and the Stars", financial information (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - "Holiday Heart", financial information (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - "The Dance of Death", financial information (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - "The Matchmaker", financial information (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - "The Waiting Room", financial information (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - "Blithe Spirit", financial information (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - "The Front Page", financial information (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - "Candide", financial information (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - "Playquest", financial information (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - photographs of Zelda Fichandler (Box 191, Folder 11)
    includes photos with President Ford and Nancy Regan
  - touring information (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - misc correspondence and contracts (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - freight information for trip to Israel (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - information on Arena Stage trip to Israel (Box 191, Folder 15)
  - information on Arena Stage trip to Israel (Box 191, Folder 16)
  - USSR tour (Box 191, Folder 17)
  - The African Company (Box 191, Folder 18)
  - Actors Equity Assc. (Box 191, Folder 19)
  - "Blood Knot", financial information (Box 191, Folder 20)
  - Bob Nemiroff payments (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - misc. financial information (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - "Raisin in the Sun", royalties (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Helen Hayes awards, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - "madness" broadway production financial info (Box 192, Folder 6)